OLADIMEJI OLAYINKA TOSIN

Address: No6, Oke Abiodun Street, Oke Ata, Mango Mosafuneto, Abeokuta Ogun State. Nigeria.

Phone No: 08060264333 Email: ogoyinka72@gmail.com

PERSONAL STATEMENT:

A motivated, ambitious, determined and industrious, who desire working within a team that requires strong interpersonal and organizational skills.

CAREER OBJECTIVE:

To utilize my academic experience as well as to develop my expert in a company that encourages individual innovation, idea, and creativity. In addition, to be submissive and dedicated in order to initiate and add value to the organization standard.

PERSONAL DATA:

Date of Birth: 1st May, 1988

Sex: Male
Nationality: Nigerian
State of Origin: Oyo-State

Local Government Area: Ibadan North East

Marital Status: Single

PERSONAL SKILLS:

- Ability to learn new things and to adapt to changes
- Ability to manage people and resources
- Excellent communication skill
- Transformation of human resources into revenue target skill
- Strong analytical and problem solving skill
- Self motivation and target driven
- Computer literate

EDUCATION:

• The Polytechnic, Ibadan. Oyo State. 2014-2017 Higher National Diploma (HND) in Accounting

(Lower Credit)

• The Polytechnic, Ibadan. Oyo State. 2010-2012

National Diploma (ND) in Accounting

(Lower Credit)

Community Secondary School, Onipe, Ibadan. Oyo State.
 National Examination Council (NECO)

WORK EXPERIENCE:

November 2015 - August 2017 Customer Care Officer

ISONBPO.INT'L ABEOKUTA OGUN.

Responsibilities:

Welcoming of customer for calling the customer care.

- Request for customer queries.
- Pacify and give resolution to customer queries.
- Informing customers on new products and services of the company.
- Give customer direction on how to use the products and services.
- Close the customer call with politeness and company farewell.

September 2012 - December 2014

Sales Assistant

Foodco Nigeria Limited Jericho Ibadan Oyo-State.

Responsibilities:

- · Taking customers order.
- · Keeping of sales records.
- · Providing customer's want.
- Attending to issues concerning any products.
- Deal directly with customers both face to face and on phone.
- Monitoring day to day transaction.

TRANING ATTENDED:

DATE: Oct. 2015

TRAINER: MR.KUNLE AWOTIKU
TOPIC: CALL CENTRE AGENT JOB

VENUE: U.I Consultancy B. University of Ibadan, Ibadan Oyo-State.

Topics:

- Who is a call centre agent?
- · Customer service positive words & communication.
- Customer handling skills.
- Empathy and sympathy.
- · Questioning skills of a customer service.

DATE: October 2015

TRAINER: MR. FRANCIS AKINPELU

VENUE: Ilorin, Kwara-State. TOPIC: Work Place Ethnics

DATE: December 2015 TRAINER: MR. OWOKHO

Topic: HOW MAY I HELP YOU?

Venue: Obasanjo Glass House, Ita-Eko, Abeokuta.

Ogun State Nigeria.

TOPICS:

- Understanding different types of customer.
- What customer value.
- Opportunity of establishing a report.
- · Handling difficult customer.
- Managing self.
- Integrity.

REFEREES:

Available on Request